--- CONTENT OF Krish_Resume1 .pdf ---
Failed to read Krish_Resume1 .pdf: 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\u2714' in position 4122: character maps to <undefined>
--- CONTENT OF IN226033802 (1).pdf ---
Date: 05th February 2026
                               Sub:  Offer of Appointment as a ôAgentic AI Intern û Remoteö
Dear Binnala Hemanth (Intern ID : IN226033802),
This appointment is offered to Mr./Ms. Binnala Hemanth, a student of Aditya Institute of 
Technology and Management , as part of the internship program conducted by Innomatics 
Research Labs.
1.We are pleased to offer you an appointment in  Innomatics Research Labs  as  Agentic AI
Intern.  Your  association  with  us  will  be  governed  by  certain  confidential  information
(mentioned below section) which needs to be followed.
2.You are required to virtually join on  09th February, 2026  and the offer stands withdrawn
there after unless the date is extended and communicated to you in writing.
3.You are requested to login via registered email id on the Zoom link which has been sent
to  your  respective  mails.  You  should  report  at  06:00PM  IST  sharp  on  the  above-
mentioned date to complete the joining formalities. All the below mentioned documents
should be scanned and sent through Google form. (Onboarding Form Link is available in the
mail).
4.During  the  Internship,  you  will  be  assigned  with  Python  Programming,  FastAPI,  AWS,
LangChain and LangGraph  related Projects/Products/Trainings that will help improve your
understandings of the concepts learned. And you would be expected to put your best efforts
in executing the tasks assigned to you. These tasks will help you in upskilling yourself.
5.As  an  intern,  you will  not receive any  of  the  employee  benefits that  regular  company
employee receives.
6.We welcome you to Innomatics family  and look forward for a long term and mutually
beneficial association.
7.Please be advised that this is an unpaid internship program.
Confidentiality
During this Internship, you may come across confidential business information. By accepting
this, you acknowledge that you must keep all this information strictly confidential, and refrain
from using it for your own purposes or from disclosing it to anyone outside the company. In
addition, you agree that, upon conclusion of your employment, you will immediately return to
the  company  all  its  property,  equipment,  and  documents,  including  electronically  stored
information. Failing which you will be subjected undergo required legal procedures. Please sign
and attach a scanned copy of this Intern offer letter via same Google form, signifying your
acceptance to the terms and conditions enunciated above.
Yours Sincerely,
Raghu Ram Aduri
(Program Manager)
Innomatics Research Labs
This is to certify that I have read this Agreement and understood all the terms and conditions
mentioned therein and I hereby accept and agree to abide by them:
Date: Name:
Place: Signature:
***This is a highly confidential document hence you are requested not disclose it to anyone else
All the below mentioned documents must be submitted  (Kindly submit them via the Google
Form mentioned in email).
 
1) Signed Offer Letter
2) Self-Attested Government ID proofs
3) Passport sized color photographs
4) Updated resume

